Guide to the Cross Campus Library, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Cross Campus Library, Yale University, records
1967-1999
RU 245
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
23
The materials consist of bound lists documenting books reserved at the Cross Campus Library for courses taught at Yale, a scrapbook, and memorabilia documenting the Cross Campus Library.
Yale University. Library
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 32-D (YRG 32-D), Records of Yale school and departmental libraries and collections
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The materials consist of bound lists documenting books reserved at the Cross Campus Library for courses taught at Yale.
Academic libraries -- Reserve collections; Yale University. Library
- Undergraduate course reserve book lists, 1979-1991; Accession 1995-A-044
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Spring 1979 (AsSci 122b - German 534b) (Box 1)
  - Fall 1979 (AsSci 129a - HAL 380a) (Box 2)
  - Fall 1979 (HAL 530a - Women's Studies 295a) (Box 3)
  - Spring 1980 (AsSci 122b - HYSM 226b) (Box 4)
  - Spring 1980 - Spring 1981 (Box 5)
  - Summer 1981 - Fall 1983 (Box 6)
  - Spring 1983, Spring 1984, Fall 1985 (Box 7)
  - Spring 1985 - Spring 1986 (Box 8)
  - Spring 1987 - Spring 1988 (Box 9)
  - Spring 1989 - Fall 1990 (Box 10)
  - Spring 1990 - Spring1991 (Box 11)
- Undergraduate course reserve book lists, 1992-1993; Accession 2000-A-037 (Box 1–2)
  Scope and Contents
  No inventory available.
- Index cards documenting courses taught by faculty members, 1967-1982; Accession 2001-A-031
  - Asger - Hogenson, 1967-1982 (Box 1)
  - Holahan -Siamwalla, 1967-1982 (Box 2)
  - Sibley - Zuckerman, 1967-1982 (Box 3)
- Undergraduates course reserve book lists, 1994-1997; Accession 2003-A-008
  - Spring 1994, Spring 1995 (Box 1)
  - Fall 1994, Fall 1995 (Box 2)
  - Spring 1996, Spring 1997 (Box 3)
  - Fall 1996, Fall 1997 (Box 4)
- Undergraduate course reserve lists, 1998-1999; Accession 2004-A-003 (Box 1–2)
- Cross Campus Library scrapbook and memorabilia, circa 1970s-1990s; Accession 2009-A-104
  - Button (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Greeting cards (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Postcards (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook (Box 1, Folder 6-7)